It’s gonna be fun
あ、もう着けてしまった
Oops, I’ve got mine on already
That’s fine, it’s fine
着けても大丈夫、大丈夫
I put them on as a matter of course
すごい自然に（着けてしまった）
A hot mess, hot mess
Blow it up Listen up
息吹きかけて Listen up
숨을 내쉬고 잘 들어 봐
With my own style Fill it up
とびきり“らしさ”で Fill it up
특출나게 “나다움”으로 채우겠어
Iʼm a troublemaker, troublemaker
난 말썽쟁이, 말썽쟁이
Whatʼs so funny, funny, honey
뭐가 그리 웃겨, 허니
I got your attention
네 시선을 끌어
Sing loud, loud In a blink of an eye Time’s up
Sing loud, loud
더 크게 불러 봐 눈 깜짝할 새에 시간 다 됐어
あっという間に Time’s up
Open your blind mind
눈먼 마음을 열어 봐
Everybody waits for me
다들 날 기다려
Make the sensation
센세이션을 일으켜
In any shape or form is okay
どんな形でも Okay
어떤 형태라도 Okay
Single mindedly on my way
ひたすら On my way
한결같이 내 길을 걸어
Take it slowly
천천히 가도 돼
Ainʼt no worry
뭐가 걱정이야
Dancing with the flames
불꽃과 함께 춤춰
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it, I can take you to MY WORLD
네가 원하면, MY WORLD로 데려가 줄게
I am the one (Hot)
내가 그 사람이야 (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)」
내가 최고 (Hot)
I won’t stop anymore
止まらない もう
멈추지 않아 이제
I am the one (Hot)
내가 그 사람이야 (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
그리고 이젠 내 차례야 (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
Groundbreaking appearance
画期的登場シーン
획기적인 등장 신
Shake it Mix it My eye-catching style
Shake it Mix it 目を惹く My style
흔들고 섞으며 눈길을 끄는 내 스타일
Dazzling dimension
目が眩むほど光る Dimension
아찔할 정도로 눈부신 디멘션
Feel it coming now, feel it taking over
다가오고 있어 장악할 거야
I’ll blow ur mind like all the time
내가 계속 널 놀래 주겠어
Hidden ænergy Dream Designer
潜めた ænergy　夢のDesigner
숨은 ænergy 꿈의 Designer
Now, oh yeah, that’s right
지금, oh yeah, 그거야
So come on
그러니 다가와
Always daring
いつも攻めてる
항상 과감하게
Show you ma attitude
내 애티튜드 보여 줄게
In any shape or form is okay
どんな形でも Okay
어떤 형태라도 Okay
Single mindedly on my way
ひたすら On my way
한결같이 내 길을 걸어
Take it slowly
천천히 가도 돼
Ainʼt no worry
뭐가 걱정이야
Dancing with the flames
불꽃과 함께 춤춰
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it, I can take you to MY WORLD
네가 원하면, MY WORLD로 데려가 줄게
I never lay low, never lay low
난 절대 안 숨어, 안 숨어
U watch me glow glow, watch me glow glow
내가 빛나는 걸 보고 있어, 보고 있어
Drama has begun This is not fiction
드라마는 시작됐어, 이건 픽션이 아냐
Ready or Not
준비가 됐든, 안 됐든
Make it hot hot, make it hot hot
분위기를 뜨겁게 해 줘, 뜨겁게
Baby Iʼm on fire, Iʼm on fire
베이비 난 불타고 있어, 불타고 있어
Fire Ah Ooh
파이어 Ah Ooh
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
Story I’ve been drawing Never hesitate
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
그려 왔던 스토리 망설이지 않아
Iʼm a hot mess, hot mess
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
So if U LIKE it, I can take you to MY WORLD
네가 원하면, MY WORLD로 데려가 줄게
I am the one (Hot)
내가 그 사람이야 (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
내가 최고(Hot)
I won’t stop anymore
止まらない もう (I am the one)
멈추지 않아 이제
I am the one (Hot)
내가 그 사람이야 (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
그리고 이젠 내 차례야 (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
Know you want it some more
더 갖고 싶지
Beyond time and space Believe in yourself
時空を飛び越え Believe in yourself
시공을 뛰어넘어 네 자신을 믿어 봐
Know you want it some more
더 원하지
Open world
開かれた世界
열린 세계
Hot mess, hot mess
Performing is so much fun
やはりライブ は楽しいですね
We were so hyped up
盛り上がりすぎちゃった